<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hugo on ScopeCam MCP Documentation</title><link>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/tags/hugo/</link><description>Recent content in Hugo on ScopeCam MCP Documentation</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/tags/hugo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Documentation Compliance Check for Hugo Migration</title><link>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/documentation-compliance-check/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/documentation-compliance-check/</guid><description>Documentation Compliance Check for Hugo Migration 🟢 Active
Overview This document verifies that all files created for the Hugo static site migration comply with the project&amp;rsquo;s documentation standards and follow the established plans. It serves as a quality assurance checkpoint before proceeding with full-scale content migration.
File Compliance Matrix Configuration Files File Standard Compliance Comments config/_default/config.toml ✅ Compliant Correctly defines taxonomies, permalinks, menus, and parameters config/development/config.toml ✅ Compliant Contains appropriate development-specific overrides config/production/config.</description></item><item><title>Hugo Containerized Setup for MCP Documentation</title><link>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/hugo-containerized-setup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/hugo-containerized-setup/</guid><description>Hugo Containerized Setup for MCP Documentation 🟢 Active
↩️ Back to Hugo Migration Executive Summary
Overview This document outlines how to integrate the Hugo static site documentation system with the existing ScopeCam MCP containerized development environment. It provides configuration details for developing, testing, and building the documentation site in a containerized environment consistent with the project&amp;rsquo;s established patterns.
Prerequisites Familiarity with the Containerized Development Environment Docker or Podman installed locally Basic understanding of the Hugo static site generator Access to the project repository Container Configuration Dockerfile for Hugo Development Create a Dockerfile.</description></item><item><title>Hugo Implementation Verification</title><link>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/hugo-implementation-verification/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/hugo-implementation-verification/</guid><description>Hugo Implementation Verification 🟢 Active
Overview This document provides a comprehensive verification of the Hugo implementation for the ScopeCam MCP documentation site. It confirms that all requirements from the migration plan have been met and that the implementation is ready for full-scale content migration.
Requirements Verification 1. Documentation Structure Requirements Requirement Status Evidence Preserve dual-layer structure ✅ Implemented Content directories organized into root and MCP layers with layer-specific navigation Maintain content hierarchy ✅ Implemented Section directories created with appropriate nesting and _index.</description></item><item><title>Hugo Migration Content Checklist</title><link>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/hugo-migration-checklist/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/hugo-migration-checklist/</guid><description>Hugo Migration Content Checklist 🟢 Active
Overview This checklist provides a step-by-step guide for migrating existing documentation to the Hugo static site framework. It ensures consistent application of standards and proper conversion of content during the migration process.
Pre-Migration Preparation Document Inventory Review the Hugo Migration File Mapping document Identify all documents to be migrated in the current documentation Verify the mapping for each document to its new location in the Hugo structure Create a prioritized list of documents to migrate Document any dependencies between documents (cross-references) Environment Setup Ensure the Hugo environment is properly set up according to Hugo Implementation Steps Verify that the containerized environment is working as expected Test the Hugo server with existing sample content Ensure you have appropriate editor with Markdown preview capability Content Migration Process Step 1: Section Structure Setup Create section index files (_index.</description></item><item><title>Hugo Migration Implementation Steps</title><link>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/hugo-implementation-steps-update/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/hugo-implementation-steps-update/</guid><description>Hugo Migration Implementation Steps 🟢 Active
↩️ Back to Hugo Migration Executive Summary
Overview This document provides a detailed, step-by-step guide for implementing the ScopeCam MCP documentation migration to Hugo. The implementation process is designed to integrate seamlessly with the project&amp;rsquo;s existing containerized development environment and automation frameworks.
Prerequisites Access to the ScopeCam MCP repository Familiarity with the Containerized Development Environment Docker or Podman installed locally Basic understanding of Hugo Git and GitHub access Phase 1: Foundation Setup 1.</description></item><item><title>Hugo Migration Implementation Summary</title><link>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/hugo-implementation-summary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/hugo-implementation-summary/</guid><description>Hugo Migration Implementation Summary Status: Active Overview This document provides a summary of the Hugo static site implementation for the ScopeCam MCP documentation. Phase 1 of the migration has been successfully completed, providing a solid foundation for the project&amp;rsquo;s documentation in Hugo format.
Implementation Status Component Status Completion Hugo Framework Setup 🟢 Complete 100% Theme Development 🟢 Complete 100% Content Migration - Phase 1 🟢 Complete 100% Content Migration - Overall 🟡 In Progress 29% Deployment Configuration 🟢 Complete 100% Quality Verification 🟢 Complete 100% Core Components Implemented 1.</description></item><item><title>Hugo Migration Progress Tracking</title><link>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/migration-progress/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/migration-progress/</guid><description>Hugo Migration Progress Tracking 🟢 Active
Overview This document tracks the progress of migrating ScopeCam MCP documentation to the Hugo static site framework. It provides real-time status updates on the migration process based on the prioritization plan.
Migration Progress Summary Phase Total Documents Migrated Progress Phase 1: Core Navigation and Entry Points 13 13 100% Phase 2: Essential Technical Documentation 12 8 67% Phase 3: Supporting Documentation 17 0 0% Phase 4: Templates and References 3 0 0% Overall Total 45 21 47% Detailed Migration Status Phase 1: Core Navigation and Entry Points ✅ Document Status Date Completed Notes /docs/README.</description></item><item><title>Hugo Shortcodes Reference for ScopeCam Documentation</title><link>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/hugo-shortcodes-reference/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/hugo-shortcodes-reference/</guid><description>Hugo Shortcodes Reference for ScopeCam Documentation 🟢 Active
Overview This document provides a reference guide for the custom Hugo shortcodes available in the ScopeCam MCP documentation site. Shortcodes allow for consistent application of special formatting and components across the documentation.
What Are Shortcodes? Shortcodes are special Hugo constructs that provide a simple way to extend Markdown&amp;rsquo;s capabilities. They allow for inserting complex content or formatting without resorting to HTML, ensuring consistency across the documentation.</description></item><item><title>Hugo Site Plan</title><link>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/hugo-site-plan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/hugo-site-plan/</guid><description>Hugo Site Plan Status: Active This document outlines the plan for implementing the Hugo-based documentation site for the MCP project.
Site Requirements Core Requirements Two Documentation Layers
Root Documentation Layer (all MCP documentation) MCP Core Documentation (specific to MCP core components) Section Organization
Project (project management, plans, etc.) Architecture (architectural decisions, components) Implementation (practical guides, code structure) Standards (guidelines, coding standards) Templates (reusable documentation templates) Tools (documentation tooling guides) Content Management</description></item><item><title>Hugo Theme Design</title><link>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/hugo-theme-design/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/hugo-theme-design/</guid><description>Hugo Theme Design Status: Active This document outlines the design specifications for the MCP documentation Hugo theme.
Design Objectives The theme design is guided by these primary objectives:
Readability: Ensure all documentation is easy to read and navigate Consistency: Maintain consistent styling and interaction patterns Accessibility: Ensure documentation is accessible to all users Performance: Keep the site fast and lightweight Maintainability: Create a design that is easy to maintain and extend Design Strategy The theme will follow these design principles:</description></item><item><title>Phase 1 Content Verification</title><link>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/phase1-verification/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/phase1-verification/</guid><description>Phase 1 Content Verification 🟢 Active
Overview This document provides a comprehensive verification of all content migrated during Phase 1 of the Hugo static site implementation. Before proceeding to Phase 2, we need to ensure all created content meets the project&amp;rsquo;s documentation standards.
Document Verification Checklist The following verification has been performed on all Phase 1 documents:
Front Matter Compliance Document Title Status Version Dates Contributors Related Docs Tags Result /content/_index.</description></item><item><title>ScopeCam MCP Documentation: Hugo Migration Executive Summary</title><link>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/hugo-migration-executive-summary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/hugo-migration-executive-summary/</guid><description>ScopeCam MCP Documentation: Hugo Migration Executive Summary 🟢 Active
↩️ Back to Documentation Index
Overview This document provides an executive summary of the comprehensive plan to migrate the ScopeCam MCP documentation to a Hugo-based static site deployed on GitHub Pages. The migration will preserve the current dual-layer documentation structure while enhancing it with Hugo&amp;rsquo;s capabilities for organization, navigation, presentation, and search.
Key Benefits The migration to Hugo will provide the following benefits:</description></item><item><title>ScopeCam MCP Documentation: Hugo Migration Index</title><link>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/hugo-migration-index/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/hugo-migration-index/</guid><description>ScopeCam MCP Documentation: Hugo Migration Index 🟢 Active
↩️ Back to Documentation Index
Overview This document provides an index of all resources related to the migration of ScopeCam MCP documentation to a Hugo-based static site for GitHub Pages deployment. The migration has been carefully designed to preserve the existing documentation structure, align with project standards, and integrate with the containerized development environment.
Migration Documentation The migration plan consists of the following documents, each addressing a specific aspect of the migration process:</description></item></channel></rss>