<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Build Engineer on ScopeCam MCP Documentation</title><link>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/contributors/build-engineer/</link><description>Recent content in Build Engineer on ScopeCam MCP Documentation</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/contributors/build-engineer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Build Engineer Next Steps</title><link>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/project/build-engineer-next-steps/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/project/build-engineer-next-steps/</guid><description>Build Engineer Next Steps 🟢 Active
↩️ Back to Documentation Hub
Overview This document outlines the next steps for the build engineer to continue MCP implementation work. It consolidates information from existing plans and provides a clear sequence of tasks based on the current project state.
Current Project Status The initial implementation of the Multi-Agent Control Platform (MCP) is well underway. The following components have been completed:
✅ Project structure and organization ✅ Core MCP framework (interfaces, models, state machine) ✅ NATS messaging integration ✅ Basic orchestrator with agent management ✅ Camera integration agent with mock USB detection ✅ Python processor agent ✅ Containerized development environment ✅ Comprehensive documentation ✅ Unit testing framework ✅ Health monitoring system with metrics collection ✅ Resilience mechanisms (circuit breaker, state change listeners) Next Day Tasks 1.</description></item><item><title>Content Inventory and Migration Prioritization</title><link>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/content-inventory-and-prioritization/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/content-inventory-and-prioritization/</guid><description>Content Inventory and Migration Prioritization 🟢 Active
Overview This document provides a complete inventory of all existing documentation to be migrated to the Hugo static site framework, along with a prioritized migration order. This structured approach ensures systematic migration of content while maintaining documentation availability throughout the process.
Complete Content Inventory The following tables list all documentation files in the current structure, organized by layer and section.
Root Documentation Layer Project Documentation Current Path Hugo Path Status Priority /docs/README.</description></item><item><title>Hugo Migration Implementation Summary</title><link>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/hugo-implementation-summary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/hugo-implementation-summary/</guid><description>Hugo Migration Implementation Summary Status: Active Overview This document provides a summary of the Hugo static site implementation for the ScopeCam MCP documentation. Phase 1 of the migration has been successfully completed, providing a solid foundation for the project&amp;rsquo;s documentation in Hugo format.
Implementation Status Component Status Completion Hugo Framework Setup 🟢 Complete 100% Theme Development 🟢 Complete 100% Content Migration - Phase 1 🟢 Complete 100% Content Migration - Overall 🟡 In Progress 29% Deployment Configuration 🟢 Complete 100% Quality Verification 🟢 Complete 100% Core Components Implemented 1.</description></item><item><title>Hugo Migration Progress Tracking</title><link>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/migration-progress/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/migration-progress/</guid><description>Hugo Migration Progress Tracking 🟢 Active
Overview This document tracks the progress of migrating ScopeCam MCP documentation to the Hugo static site framework. It provides real-time status updates on the migration process based on the prioritization plan.
Migration Progress Summary Phase Total Documents Migrated Progress Phase 1: Core Navigation and Entry Points 13 13 100% Phase 2: Essential Technical Documentation 12 8 67% Phase 3: Supporting Documentation 17 0 0% Phase 4: Templates and References 3 0 0% Overall Total 45 21 47% Detailed Migration Status Phase 1: Core Navigation and Entry Points ✅ Document Status Date Completed Notes /docs/README.</description></item><item><title>MCP Containerized Development Environment</title><link>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/guides/containerized-dev-environment/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/guides/containerized-dev-environment/</guid><description>Containerized Development Environment for MCP ↩️ Back to Start Here | ↩️ Back to Documentation Index
Overview This guide details the recommended containerized development environment for the Multi-Agent Control Platform (MCP) using Podman and Podman Compose. This setup provides environment consistency, isolation, and resource efficiency while maintaining development speed.
Why Podman? Podman is particularly well-suited for the MCP development on Fedora Linux for several key reasons:
Lower Resource Overhead: Podman is a daemonless container engine that consumes fewer resources than Docker&amp;rsquo;s daemon-based approach Native to Fedora: Podman comes pre-installed or easily available on Fedora, making it a natural fit Docker Compose Compatibility: Podman supports Docker Compose files through podman-compose Rootless Containers: Podman allows running containers without root privileges, improving security Systemd Integration: Better integration with Linux systemd for service management Prerequisites Before setting up the containerized environment, ensure you have the following installed:</description></item><item><title>MCP Health Monitoring Guide</title><link>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/guides/health-monitoring-guide/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/guides/health-monitoring-guide/</guid><description>MCP Health Monitoring Guide ↩️ Back to Start Here | ↩️ Back to Documentation Index
Overview This guide documents the health monitoring system implemented for the Multi-Agent Control Platform (MCP). The health monitoring system provides real-time metrics collection, health status reporting, and resilience mechanisms to ensure system reliability and observability.
Health Monitoring Components System Architecture The health monitoring system consists of the following components:
SystemMetricsCollector: Collects JVM and system-level metrics HealthCheckService: Provides health check endpoints and manages agent health status Circuit Breaker Pattern: Prevents cascading failures during outages Agent State Monitoring: Tracks agent state transitions for health assessment NATS Health Endpoints: For querying system and agent health status Metrics Collection The SystemMetricsCollector gathers various system and JVM metrics:</description></item><item><title>MCP Testing Guide</title><link>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/guides/testing-guide/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/guides/testing-guide/</guid><description>MCP Testing Guide ↩️ Back to Start Here | ↩️ Back to Documentation Index
Overview This guide documents the testing infrastructure for the Multi-Agent Control Platform (MCP). It covers unit testing, integration testing, and health monitoring tests. The guide also provides best practices for writing new tests and running tests in both local and containerized environments.
Testing Infrastructure The MCP project uses the following testing libraries:
JUnit 5: Core testing framework Mockk: Mocking library for Kotlin Kotlin Test: Assertions and test utilities Kotlinx Coroutines Test: Utilities for testing coroutines The testing configuration is defined in the Gradle build files:</description></item><item><title>ScopeCam MCP Documentation Hub</title><link>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/readme/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/readme/</guid><description>ScopeCam MCP Documentation Hub 🟢 Active
↩️ Back to Project Root
Documentation Organization Overview The ScopeCam MCP project uses a dual-layer documentation structure that mirrors the code organization:
1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 13 14 /home/verlyn13/Projects/mcp-scope/ # ROOT PROJECT LAYER ├── README.md # Root project dashboard ├── docs/ # ROOT DOCUMENTATION LAYER │ ├── README.md # This document - Navigation hub │ ├── project/ # Project-level information │ └── guides/ # Implementation and technical guides └── mcp-project/ # MCP IMPLEMENTATION LAYER ├── README.</description></item></channel></rss>