<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Implementation on ScopeCam MCP Documentation</title><link>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/tags/implementation/</link><description>Recent content in Implementation on ScopeCam MCP Documentation</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/tags/implementation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hugo Implementation Verification</title><link>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/hugo-implementation-verification/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/hugo-implementation-verification/</guid><description>Hugo Implementation Verification 🟢 Active
Overview This document provides a comprehensive verification of the Hugo implementation for the ScopeCam MCP documentation site. It confirms that all requirements from the migration plan have been met and that the implementation is ready for full-scale content migration.
Requirements Verification 1. Documentation Structure Requirements Requirement Status Evidence Preserve dual-layer structure ✅ Implemented Content directories organized into root and MCP layers with layer-specific navigation Maintain content hierarchy ✅ Implemented Section directories created with appropriate nesting and _index.</description></item><item><title>Hugo Migration Implementation Steps</title><link>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/hugo-implementation-steps-update/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/hugo-implementation-steps-update/</guid><description>Hugo Migration Implementation Steps 🟢 Active
↩️ Back to Hugo Migration Executive Summary
Overview This document provides a detailed, step-by-step guide for implementing the ScopeCam MCP documentation migration to Hugo. The implementation process is designed to integrate seamlessly with the project&amp;rsquo;s existing containerized development environment and automation frameworks.
Prerequisites Access to the ScopeCam MCP repository Familiarity with the Containerized Development Environment Docker or Podman installed locally Basic understanding of Hugo Git and GitHub access Phase 1: Foundation Setup 1.</description></item><item><title>Hugo Migration Implementation Summary</title><link>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/hugo-implementation-summary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/hugo-implementation-summary/</guid><description>Hugo Migration Implementation Summary Status: Active Overview This document provides a summary of the Hugo static site implementation for the ScopeCam MCP documentation. Phase 1 of the migration has been successfully completed, providing a solid foundation for the project&amp;rsquo;s documentation in Hugo format.
Implementation Status Component Status Completion Hugo Framework Setup 🟢 Complete 100% Theme Development 🟢 Complete 100% Content Migration - Phase 1 🟢 Complete 100% Content Migration - Overall 🟡 In Progress 29% Deployment Configuration 🟢 Complete 100% Quality Verification 🟢 Complete 100% Core Components Implemented 1.</description></item><item><title>Implementation Guide: Component Name</title><link>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/templates/implementation-guide-template/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/templates/implementation-guide-template/</guid><description>Implementation Guide: Component Name ↩️ Back to Documentation Index
Overview Brief description of what this implementation guide covers and what the component does.
Prerequisites List prerequisites for implementing this component.
Prerequisite 1 Prerequisite 2 Prerequisite 3 Environment Setup Describe any specific environment setup needed for this implementation.
1 # Example setup commands Implementation Steps Step 1: Title of First Step Detailed description of the first implementation step.
1 // Example code for step 1 Step 2: Title of Second Step Detailed description of the second implementation step.</description></item></channel></rss>