<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Verification on ScopeCam MCP Documentation</title><link>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/tags/verification/</link><description>Recent content in Verification on ScopeCam MCP Documentation</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/tags/verification/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Doc Doctor Guide</title><link>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/doc-doctor-guide/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/doc-doctor-guide/</guid><description>Doc Doctor: Documentation Health Check System Status: Active ↩️ Back to Tools | ↩️ Back to Documentation Index
Overview Doc Doctor is a comprehensive documentation health check system designed to ensure high-quality, consistent documentation across the MCP project. It performs a variety of checks on documentation content, structure, and metadata to identify issues and provide actionable feedback.
Concept Think of Doc Doctor as a medical professional for your documentation - it performs routine check-ups, diagnoses issues, and provides treatment recommendations to keep your documentation healthy.</description></item><item><title>Hugo Implementation Verification</title><link>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/hugo-implementation-verification/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/hugo-implementation-verification/</guid><description>Hugo Implementation Verification 🟢 Active
Overview This document provides a comprehensive verification of the Hugo implementation for the ScopeCam MCP documentation site. It confirms that all requirements from the migration plan have been met and that the implementation is ready for full-scale content migration.
Requirements Verification 1. Documentation Structure Requirements Requirement Status Evidence Preserve dual-layer structure ✅ Implemented Content directories organized into root and MCP layers with layer-specific navigation Maintain content hierarchy ✅ Implemented Section directories created with appropriate nesting and _index.</description></item><item><title>Phase 1 Content Verification</title><link>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/phase1-verification/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/phase1-verification/</guid><description>Phase 1 Content Verification 🟢 Active
Overview This document provides a comprehensive verification of all content migrated during Phase 1 of the Hugo static site implementation. Before proceeding to Phase 2, we need to ensure all created content meets the project&amp;rsquo;s documentation standards.
Document Verification Checklist The following verification has been performed on all Phase 1 documents:
Front Matter Compliance Document Title Status Version Dates Contributors Related Docs Tags Result /content/_index.</description></item></channel></rss>