<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Projects on ScopeCam MCP Documentation</title><link>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/project/</link><description>Recent content in Projects on ScopeCam MCP Documentation</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Build Engineer Next Steps</title><link>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/project/build-engineer-next-steps/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/project/build-engineer-next-steps/</guid><description>Build Engineer Next Steps 🟢 Active
↩️ Back to Documentation Hub
Overview This document outlines the next steps for the build engineer to continue MCP implementation work. It consolidates information from existing plans and provides a clear sequence of tasks based on the current project state.
Current Project Status The initial implementation of the Multi-Agent Control Platform (MCP) is well underway. The following components have been completed:
✅ Project structure and organization ✅ Core MCP framework (interfaces, models, state machine) ✅ NATS messaging integration ✅ Basic orchestrator with agent management ✅ Camera integration agent with mock USB detection ✅ Python processor agent ✅ Containerized development environment ✅ Comprehensive documentation ✅ Unit testing framework ✅ Health monitoring system with metrics collection ✅ Resilience mechanisms (circuit breaker, state change listeners) Next Day Tasks 1.</description></item><item><title>Current Project Focus</title><link>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/project/current-focus/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/project/current-focus/</guid><description>Current Project Focus: Phase 1 Core Infrastructure ↩️ Back to Start Here | ↩️ Back to Documentation Index
Last Updated: March 22, 2025
Next Update: March 29, 2025
Current Sprint Priority We are currently in Sprint 1 of Phase 1 implementation, focused on establishing the core infrastructure components of the Multi-Agent Control Platform.
Primary Objectives This Week Implement FSM Framework and Agent Interfaces ⬅️ HIGHEST PRIORITY
Complete the core agent state machine implementation Implement the base agent interface Create the agent lifecycle management components Set Up NATS Messaging Integration</description></item><item><title>Documentation Directory Structure</title><link>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/project/documentation-directory-structure/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/project/documentation-directory-structure/</guid><description>Documentation Directory Structure ↩️ Back to Documentation Index
Overview This document provides a visual representation of the MCP documentation system&amp;rsquo;s directory structure. It serves as a map for navigating and maintaining the documentation.
Complete Directory Structure 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 13 14 15 16 17 18 19 20 21 22 23 24 25 26 27 28 29 30 31 32 33 34 35 36 37 38 39 40 41 42 43 44 45 46 47 docs/ ├── README.</description></item><item><title>Documentation Migration Plan</title><link>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/project/documentation-migration-plan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/project/documentation-migration-plan/</guid><description>Documentation Migration Plan ↩️ Back to Documentation Index
Overview This document outlines the plan for migrating existing Multi-Agent Control Platform (MCP) documentation to the new standardized documentation system. The migration will ensure all technical content adheres to the established structure and standards while preserving valuable information.
Current Documentation State The MCP project currently has several key architecture documents:
README.md - Project overview first-steps.md - Initial setup instructions current-plan.md - Strategic plan architecture/fsm-agent-interfaces.</description></item><item><title>Dual-Layer Project Organization</title><link>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/project/project-organization/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/project/project-organization/</guid><description>Dual-Layer Project Organization 🟢 Active
↩️ Back to Documentation Hub
Overview The ScopeCam MCP project uses a dual-layer architecture for both code and documentation. This document clarifies this organizational approach to ensure consistent development and documentation practices across the project.
Dual-Layer Project Structure The project is organized into two distinct but related layers:
Layer Purpose Primary Path Documentation Path Root Project Layer ScopeCam project that integrates MCP for microscope control /home/verlyn13/Projects/mcp-scope/ /docs/ MCP Implementation Layer Multi-Agent Control Platform implementation /home/verlyn13/Projects/mcp-scope/mcp-project/ /mcp-project/docs/ Visual Representation of Layers 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 13 14 15 16 17 18 19 20 21 /home/verlyn13/Projects/mcp-scope/ # ROOT PROJECT LAYER ├── README.</description></item><item><title>Issues Registry</title><link>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/project/issues-registry/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/project/issues-registry/</guid><description>Issues Registry ↩️ Back to Documentation Index
Overview The Issues Registry is a central catalog of known issues, limitations, pitfalls, and technical challenges in the Multi-Agent Control Platform (MCP). This document helps developers avoid common problems and provides solutions or workarounds where available.
Using This Registry Issues are categorized by component or system area Each issue has a unique identifier (e.g., MCP-ARCH-001) Status indicators show if issues are open, being addressed, or resolved Cross-references link to technical documentation with more details Status Indicators Status Description 🔴 Open Known issue without a complete solution 🟠 In Progress Issue being actively addressed 🟡 Mitigated Partial solution or workaround available 🟢 Resolved Issue has been completely resolved ⚫ Won&amp;rsquo;t Fix Issue acknowledged but won&amp;rsquo;t be addressed Core Architecture Issues MCP-ARCH-001: FSM Complexity with Many Agents Status: 🟡 Mitigated</description></item><item><title>Path Reference Guide</title><link>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/project/path-reference-guide/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.github.io/mcp-scope/project/path-reference-guide/</guid><description>Path Reference Guide 🟢 Active
↩️ Back to Documentation Hub
Overview This quick reference guide provides clear examples for correct path references across the dual-layer structure of the ScopeCam MCP project, eliminating path confusion once and for all.
Project Base Directories Layer Absolute Path Repository-Relative Path Root Project /home/verlyn13/Projects/mcp-scope / MCP Implementation /home/verlyn13/Projects/mcp-scope/mcp-project /mcp-project Documentation Directories Documentation Absolute Path Repository-Relative Path Root Documentation /home/verlyn13/Projects/mcp-scope/docs /docs MCP Documentation /home/verlyn13/Projects/mcp-scope/mcp-project/docs /mcp-project/docs Path Reference Examples ✅ Correct Path References From Root Documentation to Root Documentation 1 [Project Organization](/docs/project/project-organization.</description></item></channel></rss>